Carpenter, Jesse materials collected from Pittsburgh Glass Company /3030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jesse Carpenter materials collected from Pittsburgh Glass Company
1950-1950
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Carpenter, Jesse
/3030
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records (documents), articles, reprints, pamphlets, correspondence, reports.
Consists mostly of pamphlets, manuals, and reports from Pittsburgh Glass.
7924527
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 18, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, April 18, 2013
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5437 OH: Paul Abelson Interview Conducted by Jesse Carpenter. 5490: Jesse Carpenter Records.
Carpenter, Jesse.; Pittsburgh Glass Company.
7924527
- Materials collected from Pittsburgh Glass Co. - 1950 (Box 1)
- Administration of Merit Salary Consideration, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Annual Stockholders Meeting and Report, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  1950 Annual Report; Notice and Proxy Statement 1951
- Calendar for Drs. Carpenter and Goodwin (Box 1, Folder 3)
  June 18 through July 20, no year given
- Ceiling Price Regulation no.22, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Office of Price Stabilization, April 25, 1951
- Charter on Labor Relations for Foremen and Stewards (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Paint Division
- Directories, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Federated Associations, National Retail Lumber Dealers Association, June 1950; Distribution Facilities and Divisional Offices, January, 1951
- Forms, Blank (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Glass Lectures (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Text of lectures and lists of visual aids
- Job Analysis Manual, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Organization and Methods Department, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Department manual
- Pamphlets (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Mostly pertaining to the history of glass or the history of PPG.
- Pensions and Benefits, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Pension agreement and employee benefits booklets
- Recommended Practices for Test Administration (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Personnel testing
- Report of Interoffice Correspondence, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Regarding grievances, May 1951
- Safety Manuals, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Industrial Truck Operators; Overhead Cab-Operated Cranes
- Safety Reports, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Annual Report 1950; Monthly Report for April 1951.
- Suggestion System (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Why, What, And How Is An Executive? (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Address by Samuel L. H. Burk, Director of Industrial Relations, PPG